Tuldarr Academy of Magic
An interesting idea, creating
an academy for the children of mages.
How many students would you say
are currently enrolled?
Fifty-two children are here
to learn to control their magic,
and sixty-eight students are
studying to become mages.
Half the children will remain
at the academy to become mages,
and even less will become
appointed as royal mages.
The future of Tuldarr rests in their hands.
In addition, word got out that
Your Majesty will be giving a lesson,
so there are a number of children
from town who want to sit in.
I don't mind at all.
Please let anyone interested take part.
Thank you very much, Your Majesty.
Queen Tinasha!
What's this?!
Are you unhurt?!
The building's collapsed!
The children are trapped underneath!
Call the medics!
Step away from the building!
Those who can help, rescue
the injured and administer first aid!
Is that really my son?
If only it had been me instead...
You cannot change events
that have come to pass.
Magic can't fix everything.
You can stop time, but turning it back isn't...
Your Majesty?
Excuse me.
I leave the rest to you.
Yes.
Be unsealed and show your true form!
~ Bloodless Scars ~
You're saying you used it for yourself
after all those warnings you gave me?
I'm sorry.
I get wanting to save those children,
but you can't use it to go back
to the past every time.
Well, that's the part of you I like.
So, did you manage to save them?
It didn't activate.
It didn't?
Does that mean it's broken?
There may be conditions needed to activate it.
I'm sorry.
You can stay here until tomorrow morning.
No, I'll be leaving.
That reminds me.
It seems there's turmoil within Cezar.
Some people have been taken
to their castle, never to return,
and many others have gone missing as well.
I see. I'll be careful.
I'll be going now.
Um...
Thank you very much.
Feel free to drop by anytime.
Valt. Isn't it about time?
Cezar Military Camp
If we leave it alone any longer,
it may very well devour us, too.
I suppose.
Sounds good to me.
I'll handle things until it emerges here,
since no one else here is capable.
You can do as you like after that.
Don't expect me to control it.
That's fine.
We'll deal with it on our own.
Ynureid Fortress    Northwestern Farsas, Bordering Druza
So Cezar has made their move.
How's it look?
Most of their men are on foot,
so they're advancing slowly.
It'll be some time before they arrive here.
However...
What's wrong?
Our mages say they can sense
a strange magical power.
They all know they can't win
in a head-on fight,
so they keep trying to pull these weird tricks.
Let's take a gamble here.
Tarvo    Cezar General
Looks like Farsas hasn't caught on yet.
Looking at Druza's tactics,
it's little wonder they were defeated.
A forbidden curse to destroy
strongholds and troops is one thing,
but what were they planning to do
once that was exhausted?
Cezar won't repeat their mistakes.
We've spent many years building
our armed forces for this occasion.
Not to mention our secret weapon.
I don't see a single reason why we would lose.
What?!
What's happening here?!
Our marching soldiers are all safe, I see.
General Tarvo, what should we do?
It's of no matter. Proceed onward.
Yes!
It seems we have the right route.
G-General!
This spell Queen Tinasha taught us
to cover flat ground in fog...
It's really strong.
This is spirit magic, so regular mages
would normally be unable to cast it.
Yet she came up with a new
composition that lets us use it.
She really is something else.
I just hope nothing goes wrong.
If only Queen Tinasha could be here right now.
Th-They're...
So this is what they meant
by strange magical power?
Taken to Cezar's castle, never to return, huh?
Your Majesty!
I know.
We'll have to engage them with magic.
Not my style, but let's do it!
Mage squad!
Ready!
Fire!
There's no end to them...
That's it, Doan.
What?
Aim that at me and fire.
Hurry up.
When you do, Tinasha will take notice.
This is our last resort.
Please don't summon me like that.
You sure like to make a scene.
I was hoping to get a chance to speak with you.
I am the queen of Tuldarr,
Tinasha As Meyer Ur Aeterna Tuldarr.
We have detected the use of
forbidden magic in this war.
As such, Tuldarr has taken it
upon ourselves to intervene.
Please understand that we act here
to eliminate what should not exist,
and not in the interest
of either party concerned.
Understood.
Thanks for acting so quickly.
I'll be leaving two spirits with you,
as well as them.
I'm planning to have them serve
as an anti-forbidden-curse unit,
so please work them hard.
Tuldarr mages?
I suppose we don't know much
about forbidden curses.
Thanks.
That said, they're still trainees who
haven't faced any real forbidden curses yet.
They are excellent mages, though.
Now I'm not sure what I should think of them.
I'm off to go dispatch Simila,
the cause of these corpses.
Simila?
I remember that name
from when you got poisoned.
It's the god worshiped
by the weird cult from back then.
Or rather, it's an evil god told of
since ancient times in Cezar.
Evil god?
What's this about an evil god?
Don't tell me those really exist.
Well, I don't think it really dates back
to mythological times, like Aetea.
Still, it's some sort of accumulation
of magic and souls.
I should be fit to handle it.
If it's too much for you,
just wait and I'll be right there.
I'll be fine.
You're sure you can win, right?
Of course.
Make sure you come back alive.
Leave it to me.
I'll be awaiting your return in the fortress.
O-Oscar!
W-We're in the middle of a battle!
Yeah. Go on now.
Senn. Lilia.
I leave this in your hands.
Yes, my lady.
As you wish.
Best of luck out there.
You too.
Okay, let's go.
That... sure is something.
Simila    Evil God
It's so gross-looking...
Lady Tinasha, you're creeped out by that?
I mean, it doesn't have any legs.
And it's huge.
So you'd be fine if it had legs?
That's not what I mean.
I wonder where that's connected to.
Maybe it's a conceptual entity?
If there is a source, I'd imagine this goes
down all the way to the lowest realm.
The evil god itself looks to be composed
mostly of magic and human souls.
It's been given form through
human flesh and blood,
then manifested with a definition, I suppose?
It seems like we're dealing with
quite a talented caster.
Can't say much for their taste...
All right.
Let's give this a shot.
Fly through the night,
despair that has rejected slumber.
Be defined and appear before me.
By my command,
repeat the sequence forevermore.
H-Hey! We need a barrier!
It's no good!
We won't make it!
That thing...
It's absorbing them!
Just awful.
How frustrating.
That means makeshift restraints
will do us no good.
What now, little girl?
Can you stop the supply of energy
coming from that opening?
Not with just us two.
Maybe if there were five of us here.
Let's go with that, then.
Why do you want to cut off its supply?
L-Little girl...
You're not thinking of
absorbing that, are you?
Magic doesn't make up
a large part of its composition.
Once it loses the energy it needs to
manifest, it should disintegrate on its own.
Theoretically, sure...
But what if you absorb too much
magic and destroy your body?
I'll release the magic
if things start to look bad.
That's our only option, huh?
Eir. Nil. Sylpha.
Okay, here we go.
That's amazing.
Was it like this against Tayiri
four hundred years ago?
Not exactly.
These corpses move a lot slower,
and they burn more easily.
It's a lot easier than back then.
We don't have that many
mages in Tuldarr, either.
Soldiers on horseback would be hard to handle.
I see.
The annoying part is that
I can't tell when it'll end.
Your Majesty!
It seems Cezar has long been controlled
by Simila and the cult that worships it.
The current king obeys
every whim of the cult leader,
and all the people
who oppose his policies are killed.
To join their army of immortal soldiers, huh?
Let's get started.
Keep your eyes on me.
I am the first and last despair you will face.
Come.
Let us dance.
Be dispersed.
Is it over?
No!
Th-The pain...
Lady Tinasha!
Mila! Don't break formation!
Karr!
We need to tear that thing off, right now!
It'll use the magic
she absorbed to take control!
If you abandon the spell,
we'll lose all our chance of victory!
Have a little more faith in her!
There's more to the world
than what we can observe.
Untold numbers of invisible layers
on top of one another.
We refer to these as "planes of existence."
From heavenly virtues to the negative deep.
All of it is contained in this one world.
Someone told me that before.
Although I can't say what "before" is, exactly.
It's very dark here.
I can't see a thing.
My name is undefined.
Are you waiting?
Lady Tinasha!
Ow!
I haven't ached this much
in four hundred years...
Of course not.
You're saturated with magic.
We'll handle everything else.
You go ahead and rest up.
Thanks...
Does this mean she's done it?
That seems to be the case!
Then let's clean up and get out of here.
Yes!
I'm getting sick of seeing all these corpses.
How are you feeling?
I'll be good as new once I get some sleep.
Thanks for your concern.
I'm off to help Mira with the aftermath
before she snaps at me.
The little lady's in your hands, Miss Mage.
You can leave her to me!
What happened, exactly?
You see...
My memories are hazy.
I was in a strange place
where I understood everything.
But I can't remember it anymore.
That happens a lot with dreams.
You start to forget them
as soon as you wake up.
Yeah, exactly.
Still, that should have dealt some
serious damage to the Cezar army.
Now the corpses are dead.
Which means His Majesty
should be returning soon.
I'll have to make this quick, then.
I'd rather not face the wielder of Akashia.
Sylvia!
How dare you!
You shouldn't be straining yourself.
You can rest up all you like once we get there.
We still have plenty of time.
Tinasha's been kidnapped?!
Was it a man with silver hair?
No, it seems she didn't get
a good look at his face.
He was clad in black mage robes.
Karr! This is your fault!
Why didn't you stay with Lady Tinasha?!
My bad.
Excuse me?!
Tinasha and I are the only ones at fault here.
Can you track where she is?
Actually, I can't sense her magic at all.
Either she shut it off herself,
or an incredibly powerful seal's been placed.
For both the attempted poisoning and
the Delilah case before Tinasha's coronation,
we received word that
a male mage was behind it all.
There was a man who matched
his description very closely.
The one who came to Farsas posing as a Yarda
royal mage, only to suddenly disappear.
We know it was a Simila worship cult
that sent Delilah to begin with!
Valt was behind it all, then...
He was after Tinasha from the very start!
~ Joyful Sorrow ~